showtimes.com 2009-05-12

# Privacy Statement for Hollywood.com at Hollywood.com

Hollywood.com, LLC. ("Hollywood.com") has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: 

By accepting this _Privacy Policy_ and our _Terms of Use_ , you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in the manner prescribed in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to our terms of use. 

This Privacy Policy contains a number of references to other information pages on our Site and other websites. Please note: underlined words and phrases are click-through links to these pages and websites. We strongly recommend that as you read this Privacy Policy, and you click on such links to obtain further important details about the Privacy Policy, as they may contain further terms and conditions which apply to you. 

Please note that your Information will be stored and processed on our computers in the United States. The laws on holding personal data in the United States may be less stringent than the UK laws but we will hold and transmit your Information in a safe, confidential and secure environment. We will never sell or rent your personal information to third parties except as described in this Privacy Policy. If you object to your information being transferred or used in this way please do not register or provide us with such information. If you have any questions, send an email to [membership@boca.hollywood.com](mailto:membership@boca.hollywood.com)

 **Overview**

Your Privacy is very important to us. As part of the normal operation of our services we collect and, in some cases, may disclose information about you. This Privacy Policy describes the information we collect about you and what may happen to that information. As described below, some of your personally identifiable information is disclosed to third parties and used by us and third parties. By accepting the Privacy Policy, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personally identifiable information. 

**Information Collection, Use, Sharing and Disclosure**

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our websiteadver and services. Through customer surveys, subscriptions, and newsletter registrations, our site may request users to give us contact, demographic and/or financial information (such as their name, locale, gender, age, income level and email address). The demographic information is used, among other things, to enhance user experience so we can be more content specific. The contact information is used to notify users of new services and content, as well as for surveys and newsletters. Our site may use an order form for customers to subscribe to our for-pay services. We collect contact information (like e-mail address) and financial information (like account or credit card numbers). Contact information from the order form is used to send billing invoices. Contact information is also used to get in touch with the subscribers when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future communications; see the choice/opt-out section below. Financial information that is collected is used, among other things, to bill the user for products and services for in-house statistics, advertising, and marketing target information. We will never share personal financial information with any other parties without your consent. Information collected during Hollywood.com subscriber registration is used for in-house statistics, marketing target information, and advising clients of Hollywood.com news and information. This site contains links to other sites. Hollywood.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites or any website from which you may have linked to Hollywood.com. 

Hollywood.com is committed to protecting your privacy online. Please read this privacy policy to fully understand how we will make use of the personal information you share with us. Hollywood.com collects certain personal information in order to provide you with customized services, content, and advertisements. Some personal information is gathered when you register to receive certain Hollywood.com products or services. We may disclose to third parties certain aggregate information contained in your registration data or related data, provided that, such information will NOT include personally identifying information, except as specifically authorized by you or in the good faith belief that such action is reasonably necessary to comply with the law, legal process, or to enforce the terms of service. Hollywood.com will also use your personal information for the purposes of providing you with any services to which you subscribe, and any service-related activities such as collecting subscription fees from you for those services, and notifying you or contacting you regarding any problem with, or the expiration of, such services. In this regard, it may be necessary for Hollywood.com to disclose your personal information to one or more agents and contractors of Hollywood.com and their subcontractors, but such agents, contractors, and subcontractors will be required to agree to use the information obtained from Hollywood.com only for these purposes. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. Hollywood.com will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited email. Also remember to sign out of your Hollywood.com account and close your browser window when you have finished your work. This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence if you share a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place like a library or Internet cafe. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, Hollywood.com cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. Hollywood.com reserves the right to change this statement at any time by posting revisions on the Hollywood.com web site. This privacy policy is not intended to, and does not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of us. 

We may run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (such as their name and email address) and demographic information (such as their zip code, age, and/or income level). The user's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary, such as if they win a contest or to notify users of upcoming contests. There are three primary types of contests: (1.) We host solely and all information that is collected stays in-house. (2.) We may share address information with third party for shipping purposes. (3.) In some rare instances, a third party may host the contest and all information is then shared. In our contest registration, we give our users the opportunity to sign up for the Hollywood.com newsletter. However, users may opt-out of receiving future mailings by selecting the "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of the newsletter. Hollywood.com products and services are directed at an adult market, and therefore this site is intended for use by adults only. Hollywood.com encourages parents to take an active role in their children's use of the Internet, and to inform them of the dangers of providing information about themselves over the Internet. Children of any age should always ask a parent for permission before sending personal information to anyone online. No information should be submitted to or posted on this web site by users under 18 years of age without the consent of their parent or guardian. Children are not eligible to use our services and we ask that minors (under the age of 18) do not submit any personal information to us. If you are a minor, you can use this service only in conjunction with your parents or guardians. 

Due to the existing regulatory environment, we cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. By way of example (without limiting the foregoing), we may be forced to disclose information to the government, law enforcement agencies or third parties under certain circumstances, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, or users may abuse or misuse your information that they collect from our Site. Therefore, although we use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personally identifiable information or private communications will always remain private. 

**Children**

Users that Hollywood.com knows to be under the age of 13 are hereby required to provide the e-mail address of their parent or guardian to [membership@boca.hollywood.com](mailto:membership@boca.hollywood.com) so that Hollywood.com may alert the parent or guardian of their child's use of this web site. The parent or guardian must consent to Hollywood.com's collection of their child's personal information. A known child user will be restricted from providing personal information until such consent is received. No information collected from users known to be under age 13 will be used for any marketing or promotional purposes outside Hollywood.com. If Hollywood.com collects personally identifiable information from children, it will do so in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Policy Act of 1998 (U.S.C. 6501 et seq.). 

**Advertisements**

Ads appearing on this web site are delivered to you by either (a) one of our web advertising partners or (b) by us. Information about your visit to this site, such as the number of times you have viewed an ad, your browser type (for example, Netscape or Internet Explorer), the type of computer operating system you use (Macintosh or Windows, for instance) and whether or not you responded to the ad delivered, (but not your name, address, phone number or other personal information), is used to serve advertisements to you on this site. We may use your zip code or geographical location information to serve advertisements to this site. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. We aggregate (gather up data across all user accounts) personally identifiable information and disclose such information in a non-personally identifiable manner to advertisers and other third parties for other marketing and promotional purposes. However, in these situations, we do not disclose to these entities any information that could be used to identify you personally. Certain information, such as your name, email address, password, credit card number, and bank account number, are never disclosed to marketing advertisers. This site may use its own proprietary ad serving system. However, this site may use and allow for third party ad serving systems (i.e.: Double-click, Mediaplex, Atlas, Zedo, etc.). Third party ad serving systems are approved at the site's discretion. The site and its third party servers collect and store anonymous data, typically through the use of cookies. 

**Public Forums**

This site contains message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. We request users to give us contact information, such as name, email, address, occupation, and interests to be a registered bulletin board user. This information is optional and not necessary to post messages. This information may be used by the administrator to send the user email notices. However, users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and users should exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information. 

**Security**

While Hollywood.com cannot guarantee that unauthorized access will never occur, we do take great care to insure that your private information is as safe as possible through the use of secure technology and internal processes. As an example, any information that we collect about you is stored in an access-controlled environment, preventing access by unauthorized people. Also, any time your information is passed across the Internet, it is protected by the use of encryption technology such as SSL (see [http://www.ssl.com](http://www.ssl.com/) to learn more about SSL encryption). Your account is also password protected, and allows you to modify or update your information at any time. 

**Choice/Opt-Out – Your ability to opt-out and remove your information.**

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. 

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service: 

  * Users can send email to [membership@boca.hollywood.com](mailto:membership@boca.hollywood.com)
  * Users can visit the following URL: <http://www.hollywood.com/content/newsletter.aspx>
  * Users can send mail to the following postal address: 2255 Glades Road. Suite 221A, Boca Raton, Florida 33431 
  * Users can call the following telephone number: (561) 322-3449

 **Correct/Update – Your ability to update your information.**

The site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided: 

  * Users can send email to [membership@boca.hollywood.com](mailto:membership@boca.hollywood.com)
  * Users can visit the following URL: <http://www.hollywood.com/content/newsletter.aspx>
  * Users can send mail to the following postal address: 2255 Glades Road, Suite 221A, Boca Raton, Florida 33431
  * Users can call the following telephone number: (561) 322-3449. 
  * This policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically. 

**Contacting the Website**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you can contact: 

Hollywood.com, LLC  
2255 Glades Road   
Suite 221A   
Boca Raton, Florida 33431   
or email us at [membership@boca.hollywood.com](mailto:membership@boca.hollywood.com)
